https://bbxhale.com/privacy/

Privacy | Benefits Brokers Exchange, Inc.
In Houston:
(713)-784-2422
info@bbxhale.com
Home
Why BBX?
Why BBX?
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, Address, Email Address, Phone Number and other information we feel is important or necessary.
What information do we collect?
We may collect personal information when you use one or more of the features offered through our Site or Applications. The following are examples of how we might collect such information:
We collect personal information from you when you register on the Site or Applications, request a quote, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another Site or Application feature.
When ordering or registering, we will ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or other information. In order to access our Applications, you will need to provide a valid e-mail address.
As with many websites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our Websites. Please refer to the “Do we use ‘cookies’?” section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
When using the Applications, we may collect information regarding your use of the Application, including but not limited to your usage, uploaded photographs, selections and creations through the Applications, as may be more specifically described in the Application Terms of Use.
The Way We Use Information:
We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to process your request. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website to join our mailing list and request general information on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Our Commitment To Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How are changes to our Privacy Policy communicated?
We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any substantive changes, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and the Applications, and may provide notice by posting a notice on the Site and/or sending e-mails to those whose e-mail address we have. Your use of the Site or Applications after such changes constitutes your agreement to the new policies. You should periodically read this Privacy Policy to learn of any revisions. Your use of the Site or Applications at any time is deemed to constitute your agreement to all of the terms of this Privacy Policy then in effect.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us or email us at info@bbxhale.com
Find Us BBX, Inc.
Search for:
Secure Site
Home
Why BBX?
